Well that's just wet your appetite as we go into the men's 10,000 meters.
A field of 29 athletes take to the track. It's a big field. It's a mighty strong one.
We had a wonderful women's 10,000 meters and wonder whether the men will follow the same pattern.
We have a huge contingent of East African talent, the great Kenanissa Bakedi.
He's had a time out from injury but with every race this year he's been getting better.
He holds the Olympic record and won in Beijing just outside 27 minutes.
He's here again. He's got his younger brother Tareku here as well.
Let's have a look down that coolest of runners on that first page after he's looked out for.
We've got Gerson A to D.C. of Eric Traier.
He's a third and fifth in previous Olympic finals.
We've got the Geberi Marium for the World Cross Country Champion Tareku Beckily.
Mo Farah, European Champion two years ago.
The British athlete who's highly favored here to win both the five and the 10.
We've got good Americans there in Tegin Tampin, Ritz and Hyne and Gallen Rock there ahead of that field.
Kennedy's a Beckily one of the greatest athletes of all time, the Ethiopian bidding for yet another major title.
And the Kenyans are strong with Wilson Kiprov and Moses Massai.
And also young Karoki as well in the lineup.
Fastest time in the world this year.
That's Kiprov's time in Eugene and he's seven minutes one point nine eight.
This is Big Field tape with two rows of athletes.
Looking here at O.A. Kool, a red candle with that new 3-1-1-0.
He's a huge fan of the European bronze and silver medalist Gallen Rock coming across there.
The American, who now trains with Farah in the coaching of our better Salazar in Oregon and USA.
And so, actually a two-brother as well.
Got the double commonwealth champion, the zero of the standardness Kiprov.
And the top Kenyan runner this year.
Next to him, we have the great Kennedy's a Beckily.
The man who succeeded highly-gebra salacing is the world's greatest distance runner.
Beckily four times world champion of 10,000 meters.
Christy Olympic champion.
And he goes to the history of it for the third win.
Moses Masai, Kenyan, second in there.
They'll be their trials in Eugene.
Jacob Uganda, a rough of the USA.
Nedhin, Eric Traias, a strong East African contingent, of course.
We look back on the next group as a Rwandan, Mathieu Gov.
It's an I-11, the NCAA champion, a Canada Sato, a Teagan camper of the USA.
And there's Mo Farah.
Look at this into the wall.
The crowd have already had a British gold medalist today.
Can they get another?
The Wanderbred to Ritok Kepelw.
Next to him, coming off every champion.
And seeing the United States through there.
Moses Kitsero.
Let's get it, Mariam.
And the world's cross-country champion.
Four from the Kiprov's and last time.
Zero there, next to Pietro, or Ecuador.
Which can champion the whole range of distances.
Geveranarium, fifth fastest in the world this year.
Wrong Ethiopian trio, of course, for the Beccolies and Geveranarium.
Took a lot to make the Ethiopian team.
The world champion didn't make it.
So they see of Ethiopia, hasn't run a 10 this year.
But always a man to look out for.
Great record over the roads and the track.
Alutabi of Saudi Arabia, the Vovsky of Ukraine.
Uchiere Katoke, the third of the canyons that we've seen now in this lineup.
Vincent Lawrence of Australia and Mark Boudre,
the Bahrain test-out there to the whole of Australia.
Completing this lineup.
A race to save up.
29 men.
At the start, the men's 10,000 meters.
The noise and the stadium, the London community for the final round of the world.
The farrow looking happy.
Great deal resting on his shoulders, but he's been in wonderful form over the last two years.
10,000 meters.
What do you want?
Start as much, when not happy, someone's put must have been on the line.
There's only 25 laps to go.
But then a little smile and nervous smile.
What sort of forms are you in?
We don't know yet.
But as this race gets underway, let me just report to you that
you remember great names in the past.
Papua Nuremi of Finland in 1920.
Emile Zattepek won this in London in 1948.
He won it again in 1952 in Helsinki.
And then of course 72 and 76 lasted.
Viran won twice.
And then Highly Capricilassi in 1906 at Lanter in 2007.
Highly Capricilassi, the great Ethiopian won that race.
And then the man who we've already seen here, out in the front here for a change.
Kenanisa Bikali of Ethiopia won it in Athens in 2004.
And again four years ago.
So he's going for a close consecutive one, but I'm not seeing Bikali take the lead.
This season at all.
And Moffara knows the danger and goes along with him.
He certainly does.
Well, when we're going to want to attack, it's not going to be in this race.
And probably we'll see back here.
It's raging really.
Fall back, Farah.
And then maybe.
And let's see what the pace is.
Pretty good.
65 and a half second first lap.
I think they'll obviously take a lap at two to circle down, but we'll finish off the long jump.
Sixth and final jump for Mitchell Watt from Australia.
He's in the silver medal position.
Can he get towards Rutherford by even getting closer with his jump?
It's great height.
Again, he's getting over his own silver line mark that's graphic on the sand pit.
It gets the right flag.
But he may rule the day because he only got going really in that fifth round where he went 8-13.
Very good on the board.
Great height off the board.
Didn't possibly get as much leg extension as he would have liked at the height of that parabola in the jump.
Just waiting for the score to come up in the distance to come on the board.
He increases his position in silver 8 meters 16.
Can they us there?
Of course, the best of 8-11.
He's in fourth position.
Watt going back to Watt, that was 8-16.
That put him securely in silver medal position.
Until there goes 7-98.
We're just waiting to confirm that.
7-98.
So he stays in fourth position.
The last jump has come up but it's still there.
Beculate coming up now to the kilometer point.
254-88.
After the first lap, he pays slow to bit.
We can just run down this advantage following him.
The last lap, 73.2.
The Cailley brothers sitting in their kip rocks there.
The Darra is there.
Sato is there.
Mass eye everyone because it has slowed down significantly.
And Will Clay is the only man who can take Greg Rutherford off the top of this long jump list.
He currently holds the bronze medal position with the 8-12.
He's 4 centimeters behind Mitchell Watt of Australia.
Well, he leaves his control.
So Rutherford raises his hands with the finger pointing upward.
He doesn't have to take his 6-round jump.
He is the Olympic champion in the men's long jump.
What a great result for the young Britain.
Well, a good evening for Britain so far with two gold medals.
And the tap on the now in the long jump.
And with no farot in the 10,000 meters, this could be one of the great nights for British athletics, certainly.
But there are an awful lot of talent there, but it has slowed down.
And you know, if it does slow down, then no farot has got all the kit for fast finishing.
You can run it from however he wants.
He's in the middle of that pack now.
He's dropped right back.
Cananisea Bikali now in about 5th place.
And that's kip rock leading at the moment.
And very happy to do so.
And no one is prepared to push this along yet.
And Greg Rutherford now can enjoy that position of being top of the pile in the men's long jump.
It's a little bit of surprise.
Both the Britain's were fancy to do well in this competition.
But to come out with the gold medal before you take your 6th jump, what a position to be in.
He can just go for it.
And it doesn't really matter.
He's now going to salute the crowd, milk it for whatever is worth.
Puffs his cheek out.
He is a really nice young man.
He's a pleasant young man and he truly deserves this.
He's had his injury problems.
He's had all sorts of problems.
He's come back this season and I've never seen him consistent as he was this season.
And really whilst the long jump competition is in general, I've been at low-ed,
you can only compete against what is here.
Absolutely.
And if we did a statistical analysis with his personal best of 835 this year
and jump in 831 tonight, he'd be the closest to his personal best without any doubt.
All the other jumpers jumping below form.
But Rutherford has nailed it tonight.
He has won the long jump gold medal London 2012.
You'll see the graphic with the final results.
He's got the top Mrs. Roney.
He's holding up the British flag.
And as Sturt and Peter has said, two gold medals in the stadium tonight from Great Britain.
And with Moffara running in the 10,000, could it be three?
So there you go, Greg Rutherford.
Winner, men's long jump.
Eight litres, 13.
Go ahead and find his coach.
Coming up to 20 laps to go and to Dessa and Maiden, the Eritreans have gone to the front
and they said, come on, let's have a race here.
The Kalees, their Kiprop is inferred.
The Kalees in forth and really it's now starting to wind up and it's all down to the former World Cross Country Champion.
I watched him in Mumbasa win the World Cross Country title in the heat of that country and look at this.
It's opened out and all of a sudden there are four moving away and there is a gap but it's very, very early days.
We've got about 19.5 laps to go.
Well, Dessa has often done this in major races, taken on the race.
Very, very slow opener, 254.88, the first kilometre and then 304.68 second kilometre only just inside six minutes.
But losing a shoe there, stopping to put it on.
That's Moses Kitsero of Uganda where he's got time to catch up and he's right at the back of the field.
Yeah, he is. I watched him win two titles and the Commonwealth Games.
He had a scintillating speedy really dead in the final stages.
There it is. There's his trip, actually, he's gone down and that's unfortunate for him but he'll have to come back.
He's experienced enough to come back very, very slowly.
The Eritrean leads and no far as back in about 12th place but this is early days indeed with 18 laps to go.
The 61.95 lap there is 69 before and then before then we had 75 second laps.
Yes, indeed. That's rhythm-sapping. That hurt.
Once you start putting that sort of pace in, if it's sustained and that's a murky of Italy moving alongside Mo Faradayr down that back straight.
The Faradayr is playing very sensibly. He's not gone with his lead. He's just gradually I hope, I expect trying to pick his way up.
As indeed is the case for some of the other big names in this race but to DC, it's not to be underestimated.
There's 242 eight there, that third kilometer after a 304. That's a very, very big game.
As we run down that distance behind the Faradayr one nine behind the leaders.
It's an on-mass Ivy Canyon further back still in 14th place.
And here's amongst the Pass of Runners that we've got two Ethiopian's here.
Third and fifth in this line up. The other one, Gabri Mariam, very much towards the back of the field with only five men behind you.
There was some kick rock. The fastest time in the world this year.
There's now been overtaken. Bekeli is really latching on. Only got one withdrawal and that is Ma'Boul of Bahrain.
He's gone. So often happens at Al-Tabi and that shot there is in about eighth place.
Night plays and Mo Farad still in a very good position to attack here.
I think he's alongside Ruppas and he's a training part of the moment.
There they are.
Americans together there.
There are two Americans being taken camp in Witsonhine of course in this race.
Interesting how they do Bekeli brothers are making a very prominent part in this race to Desey, the Aretrean leading out.
They're the Bekeli brothers behind them. This is the rest of the pack, the Kenyans, biting their time.
The three of them pretty much together around the tenth to twelve places.
They've done a lot of work with the two Aretreans. Desey, the leading of the two, Nadine.
Well, these were 30 seconds in the Olympics last year.
The four years ago, so up and did a bit better than that this time.
12th in the World Championships and then we're holding Berlin.
Mo Farad looks to me as though he's starting to make a little bit of a play now and moves slowly but surely up the field.
But he has got a terrific sprint finish in the end but so has Bekeli but we don't know what sort of form Bekeli's in.
On the evidence of the season, it's not we're not sure.
Well, it's not what he's done before but the evidence also shows you that we get a better every race.
Racine's off in the form. The moment, the younger brother, Toreco is in second place.
Ken and Ese is fourth. Look at the way the Kenyans are coming up. So Farad, two Farad, they've been running a more even place.
Gizero having a fallen and put his shoe back on. He's there.
It's out of rock and farad, so clear the big name is there.
Hello, Toby.
I'm Cassadio Rabia is also there in what was the sixth place at the moment.
And the race beginning to evolve now quite nicely.
11, 23, 1, 6. The time there at the 4 kilo-meter point.
Yeah, last that 64.3 on the official computer.
It did get to a quick one of 61-9 but they're running it more steadily and gradually catching up on the leaders.
Mass eye just ahead of Farad and Kiprop.
And those are Kiprop and Mass eye. The two fastest in the world this year.
Yeah, Mass eye close fourth last time. 4 years ago was me in that 10,000-meter final.
So he's got a sister who's quite good to live in that Mass eye.
He's made some championship wins in the past.
And Moe Farad just sitting back.
I mentioned several times not because he's British but because of what he's achieved this season thus far.
And the way in which he races, and I honestly believe that he could well have the pace.
And the rest know this. They know him and they know him well.
It's their dinner in the world championships last year.
They didn't really know him. And he took a lot of people by surprise.
Looking here at Mewchi together with Kiprop, the Italian.
Also haven't mentioned these very prominent Alutair B of Saudi Arabia and the white vest there on the inside.
But the four just been getting to collect together again or a lot of the portion of the field.
So doing the today's scene so often very returning front runner.
He's often just missed out on the top medals but he's very consistent.
Particularly good at the half-hour from his role of course.
Well we're coming up to 13 laps to go in this 10,000-meter final and it really is beginning to wind up quite nicely now.
It's anybody's race really.
To Desi has done the former World Cross-Candruc Temsha.
Sadly was the bronze medalist in 2004 in Athens over 10,000.
So he's got the experience but he does so often lead.
He's now had that lead taken away from him.
The pace is generally hotting up.
It really is.
Well they're coming up to the halfway point now.
They're coming up to 200 meters to the back.
It'll be outside 14 minutes but they can expect it very much quicker than the second half.
Let's just take a check of that five kilometers time.
14 minutes, 5.79.
So it's definitely going to be a quicker second half.
It certainly is just looking at the...
This is materi Karoki of Kenya.
It was a third of the tenions.
He's decided to take it up.
From to DC.
From to equal dec
Then we've got test powder.
Another Irritation coming up.
And here comes Mofara alongside to take close order at the front.
And that's very sensible just staying wide out of the trouble.
The two Erochians back in business again but I think they're playing in the hands of Farah.
I really do.
The other tenions at the moment, those kick-off and mass eye hanging back at the moment.
There's some way down from the lead.
You're just looking at...
I look at them in fact there.
Mass eye weighs 2,311 and kick-off 2,301.
Let's kick-off the leading if there are two tenions there.
That's going wide.
Mofara getting into position.
Shooter with the Randall also there.
And that will be staffers in the first.
Good day, sir.
Pushing on again.
He's determined he's a very tough customer today, sir.
Has it run at 10,000?
It's a weekly backer here.
Following him, can we sit just in the middle?
There's behind Farah at the moment there.
Moving past the line, just looking just jockey because it's the moment.
Making sure they're in a good place but whenever the real burst comes,
did they see, tested them out there?
We sit so 67 and a half having had a sub 62 lap early on.
Yes, they've certainly left it down to what is virtually a 5,000 metre race here.
And with 15,000 metre qualities for some of these athletes, certainly.
We know one or two of them can sprint at the end and run,
but whether that speed run out of them, a little nudge there.
Mofara complaining about Megan.
Megan, Megan was just leaning on him a little bit there.
Megan really pushing on Farah.
He's saying, the space there I want to come in.
There's a real backer going on between the two of them.
Just drop your shot.
We were searched for a mass eye coming up now.
Ekemiens are really running as a team I think here.
And materials had his time in the leading canyon,
and our mass eye is coming up.
Very interesting tactics.
Ethiopian's prominent, Kenyans prominent, and the three are a trayants.
Very prominent.
Well, Farah's dropped back about five or six places to get himself out of trouble
and trying to wind out wide.
But to Eritrea one and two, Kenyah three, Ethiopia four.
And tell you what, it's beginning to hot up a little bit now.
Now, one of the 246 kilometers there.
So, in this locking position, not as quick as earlier in the race,
there's a lot of moving back and forth, particularly now by the Kenyans.
And look at the way the Kenyans have moved up into the lead now.
This could be significant.
And we're certainly going to have a go, aren't they?
And kick rock.
Yes, kick rock's taking it on.
That's an amazing race, but there's still a lot of people in there.
In fact, it's mass eye.
Sorry, there's a rupture there, but it's mass eye that's taken it on.
Yes, kick rock is on.
And which is clear is that the second of the Kenyans,
I could probably just saw them on the screen.
But it is the other two Kenyans working together, I suggest.
Kick rock at the moment, I was happy to stay back.
A long side carry.
Very much those two together.
It's interesting, isn't it, that Kenyans are becaly now has moved up.
Remember, he's won this title twice.
And he's really starting to wind it up, but I tell you what,
it's Tarek Leigh, the calie, who's moved up into third place to take those order.
That'll drop out there.
And this race of attrition, we've actually losing athletes, one by one.
It wasn't kick rock, was it?
It was kick rock.
It was kick rock indeed.
So that's a major shot.
Kick rock out, 18 in a pit, and it's into the race.
Well, I thought he was just fighting his time, and it seems it wasn't right for him today.
Look, cherry leads.
Mass eye in second, but Kayleigh, third.
Then in four places, Eric, out of Turkey,
I haven't mentioned him too much.
Former Kenyans, of course.
And if no Farah is going to get involved here, he needs to take closer order,
I think, the just eight laps to go.
Still lots of time, as Armadolu's contact on the back of that group.
Well, the whole group now, what's on 25 metres from the first to the end of that group.
And Mass eye in Peruki.
And a two-week Peruki, as you can see here, in front.
Farah now moving through the field, up onto the shoulder, the two-air atrians.
Now the Kenyans, one and two.
Kenyans of the Kayleigh is in fifth place at the moment.
And Mo Farah now moving up into eighth position, as they come into the straight
into the show, there are seven laps to go.
Crossed this kilometer of the race there, a two-fourty, taking up to seven-k in 1942-58.
Now I look and go, he's coming out from the back of his.
That one, Waporsi, is training companion, the American there, in four places.
So, Mass eye leads with seven laps to go.
From Peruki, Michuri, in second place.
The Bekelies are third and fifth, they're not between them.
Farah is in sixth place.
Certainly the younger of the Kayleigh's Tadakoo,
world indoor champion at 3,000, three years ago, these come on since then, isn't he?
7.03 is best time, but this is about championship running, and it's all changed.
Kenia, Kenia, Ethiopia, USA, Ethiopia, working Ethiopia.
The Terracan, maybe not to DC, just losing a bit of ground maybe now,
having been prominent early on, the EC back in seventh place.
It's a very good performance, the Scarborough Rucks certainly.
And you know, when you look at Aberta Salazar's stable,
well, they're all up there in the first half, it goes in both of them.
Mo Farah, the second, but Rucks having a race of his life at the moment,
but then at this pace, one would expect him to be there.
The only thing that they've got to watch out for the Farah finish is just ahead now of the second of the Ethiopians that Medine.
As we look, looking there at Kamil and Livins, the NCAA champion of the Canadian, just tucked in there.
Get Ramirez well at that point.
Well, the Kenia's are working together, McCury looking around,
saying to Massiah, hey, if you're turn now, but of course, one of the great shocks is that
pick-ups not there with them.
So now Massiah's turn to take it on.
If Farah watches it and so does Beckily,
what also in the red of the USA, Massiah leads to equal Beckily as in second place.
Farah and what are together, then the other Kenia,
and what are the two Ethiopians also still up there in that leading path.
Because now we're down to 12 men getting away from the last of all.
There's certainly the medallys that can come from here, as Farah moves up onto the shoulder of Tally Gwbikelli.
Just past his team as the training partner, rock of the United States with Massiah leading.
And this is McCury, that's Kenia, he's sitting in behind, and Mo Fah.
65 and a half second left.
So we're all fireworks, just move that to tempo a little bit.
As you can see by that big group together, we're just waiting for a major move.
And certainly with great Britain two gold medals on this evening here in London.
It could be a third here because Farah looks very sharp indeed, is prepared well for this.
He's come up a world championship and now desperately needs to move it up.
He looks comfortable to miss.
So does Rapp on the inside there, Beckily looking round at him.
And now Farah takes the lead for the first time.
Four laps to go.
Massiah holding him up, with the pace slowed again.
67-1-7. Still no major move.
Well I think that shoots Farah because of its slows.
He's got the pace.
I've said several times and Rapp is having a really good ratio.
Tactically he's having a very good race.
And I just have a feeling that all of the sudden there's going to be a break.
Here comes Medina, very, very quickly indeed.
And the open's now moving up into the lead now.
Tariku but Kayleigh follows.
And he's got the Gabbry Mariam.
He's finding his time at the back of the pack.
Has now come right the way up.
And the two Gabbry's.
But that's wearing number nine on the side is Gabbry Mariam.
And he's indeed Gabbry Mariam.
And he's been sitting back there and he's waiting to see what the others are going to do.
And they're all bouncing.
And this is a real situation we have here because in close proximity nobody's prepared to take the early move.
Three laps to go.
The Daces still strong on the outside there.
The Clurro.
Still no real move.
Still the pace remains fairly slow.
Gabbry Mariam.
And if you open has come up to help the Beckelies.
Farrow and Rapp pretty much together.
And Rapp jumped third place there for Farrow.
And Rapp just behind him.
And the two Kenyans.
For Loki and Massai there.
And this will just be back to be Lack.
Farrow just checking round.
See what's going on.
As to Rico Beckelie.
The first of the others.
25-01 still another two-four and six there.
Still no big move.
Well they've got to be very careful.
They don't trip each other up here because this is dangerous time.
Territory indeed.
Now then.
Farrow waits.
Waits for his moment.
The Kenyans bunching again.
Tannik of Beckelies there.
Kenanisa still there but he's brought in on the inside.
Two laps to go.
12 men in the lead.
And Mopara shows in front.
But the three-hour try-ons are there.
The three Ethiopians are there.
And two of the Kenyans are there.
Galen Rapp is there.
This is a fascinating way.
Still no major move.
Who is going to go and win their points.
It's a very subtle wind up of the pace down the back there.
Gabriela Merlin you've got in your shot.
And Tedes is still there.
He did a lot of that early leading.
And I just think Farrow is going to make the burst soon.
I'm sure they will.
You'll have a go at it.
Ruts in close proximity.
Here goes Mopara.
Now I think it's a bit early for him to go and expose his situation.
Who is this coming up?
Ride.
Tariya Kenya.
It is.
Power looking smooth there.
Just holding this place.
Tariqa Bekali on the inside.
This is just over a lap to go now.
Galen Rapp is going well in third place.
Tariya Kenya.
The top Kenya.
Mass has behind him.
Today says five in social median.
It's the bell.
Mopara hits the bell.
28.30 seconds.
Injured a 3000 metres.
We've seen her long sprint.
Can he maintain it? He's got the might of East Africa behind him plus Gallon rock
Just behind it's parallel who leads though with less than that to go the cherry of Kenya
Beckily the two Beckilies with rock they're going away from the rest of the field
It's two on the move us to go now both are up a great Britain can this be another British goal two already today
Parallelies the field is being spread eagle behind him is Rico Beckily then is Gallon rock of the USA
Then Kenan is a backly the other Kenyan looks lost
It's no fairer coming down the home space with Beckily and rock can it be a one two for the Salazar group?
It looks like it is no parent to go for great Britain
Gallon rock tech second then the two Beckily brothers behind them
It's going to make you then it's set to go see
Grat moffara produces the goods and Gallon rock takes the silver medal a last lap of 55
Yeah, they played into his hands, but that is an Olympic champion the third gold medal for great Britain on this evening
This will go down as one of the great great evenings of British athletic certainly
Moffara forget the time it doesn't matter that was about racing and
He can't believe when he achieved this plan so well for this and at the end of the day
He came good when it mattered a brilliant brilliant last lap tactically absolutely sound
It was a very slow first 5,000 meters a negative split certainly which meant that it played into the hands
The Africans played into his hands. They really did
They knew what he'd done last year, but what a performance by him to the
American the two
Training partners come to these gangs and got two medals well
Alberto Salazar's planned them well as trained them well and they've seen them in very good stead
And they have produced the goods for him and what a night for Britain for the host nation in these Olympic games a wonderful night
Three gold medals who would have thought that
Well, there's a fascinating 10,000 a typical championship one
1405 the first 5,000 1325 the second 5,000
It's a tough way to win that Moffara is a master
He couldn't win off a long system
So all this case a fast last lap and he'll be so pleased that gallon ruff is taking this silver to Rico Beckerly took abroad
Kennedy so back a little bit fine not quite good enough this year
And he finished in fourth place then the cherry then today see them maybe
Thank you very much so the might of East Africa has been behind the might of Britain and the might of the USA
But the forefront of this 10,000 meters well
It certainly is a change isn't it because if the other dominated this
Championship for the last four Olympic games and really it's all changed now
Britain the United States
No
Worked it so well and you truly deserve this is not only a world champion is an Olympic champion
5,000 to go indeed the first ever British 10,000 meter champion as well
Another fascinating race of a great women's 10,000
Really fascinating men's 10,000 meters it was very very special
In worry of that first half he was content with the pace of those up front and really the end
He became
That's the family come to join it is indeed lovely lovely lovely moment from out
Well done dad
And the big lady too
A happy man a happy family a happy nation
It's absolutely lovely to see
And why not in Britain have the families celebrate together remember the preparations for these championships
The family have to give an awful lot of way as well
And it's a only fair that they should join in here this year
Well done, so well done
Well done indeed
And then have to tell you a bit more pictures on the front pages of the masters in the United Kingdom tomorrow
A family photo taken in a very special occasion
The occasion which this young fellow will remember for the rest of his days
And the history box will declare him the first British champion and my goodness me
It is fantastic
Well, we've got the one final event to stir it. We've got the women's 100 meters final
He seems to be running in the heat. He's also great running in the senate final and this is certainly going to be a race to save
Yes, it is and all the principles are here everyone who should be here is here
And I have to say that I have no idea who's going to take this this is one of those races where you say
Well, I'm not sure
Let's just have one more look at the final stages of what became a magnificent race in the 10,000 meters
It wasn't about time it was about tactics. It was about position. It was about everything to do with winning and
That went to Moffara of Great Britain
Ridmi wonderful
Celebration towards the end. No one is going to catch him tonight
Marvelous Marvelous Marvelous
This proud tonight
Who we're lucky to get the tickets for an evening session. I must say we'll have celebrate and there's another Olympic champion
The second of our Olympic champions tonight along with Jess Nis earlier on and rock will celebrate
To the Americas
Mal dance with anyone now absolutely anyone
Well, there's the closing stages
The light of the ringer with the light of the silver medals and the anguish and think of the men behind the might of East Africa the two
Beckley brothers
Ran well
Couldn't match the finish
Para or of rock
He's done it move to the USA to train there
Worked out at a high altitude a lot and it all come good in the wonderful series of runs over the last few years
Since his double European triumph two years ago the Farah who goes round
And a huge crowd absolutely thrilled by what they've seen here
Wow what an evening
Do hope you enjoyed all that there's a result of the 10,000 Moffara gallon look
Tarek of Beckley Kennanisa Beckley but what look at the scalcs of Africa taken by Moffara and of course gallon
Well done to him he was always in the right place at the right time
And got a very just reward there it was marbles
Well just running down the whole list of results of that men's 10,000 meters
We'll some kiprock the surprise
Non finish you're there in that race